AMEERANUR SARAEL

system analyst

Block 4, Lot 6, Kingdom Village Sinunuc, Zamboanga City, PH Filipino

0916 143 6297 asarael24@gmail.com February 24, 2002



- SOCIALS -

facebook.com/ameera.sarael instagram: @ameeranur



Diligent, organized, persistent programmer who is well-informed with systems analysis. Information Technology graduate with six months' work experience developing designing skills and data analytic for systems. Currently completing Master's in Information Technology with focus on analytics. Dedicated, adaptable, and can influence others with optimism to produce excellent results.

EDUCATION

POST GRADUATE

June 2024 – Present Western Mindanao State University

Masters in Information Technology

Normal Road, Baliwasan, Zamboanga City, PH

UNDERGRADUATE

October 2020 – May 2024 Western Mindanao State University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Normal Road, Baliwasan, Zamboanga City, PH

Academic Honoree (Cum Laude)

SECONDARY

June 2018 – April 2020 Baliwasan Senior High School - Stand Alone

Atty. Baban Drive, San Jose Rd., ZC, PH

Academic Honoree (With Honors)

June 2017 – March 2018 Basilan National High School

Isabela City, Basilan, Zamboanga Peninsula, PH

Academic Honoree (With Honors)

June 2014 – March 2017 International Philippines School in Riyadh

Olaya Street, Haymalik Fahad Rd., Riyadh, KSA

PRIMARY

June 2007 – March 2014 **International Philippines School in Riyadh**Olaya Street, Haymalik Fahad Rd, Riyadh, KSA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

April 2024 – present

IT System Analyst Novasystems

Novasystems is an IT company that provides a complete range of computing services for its corporate clients.

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Monitoring and perform tests and maintenance on servers and workstations
- Advising clients on IT issues and strategies
- Database design
- Configuration and installation of hardware and software to client's specifications
- Network administration and implementation

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

 Organized database to track business contacts and was commended for attention to detail and accuracy on July 2024

ACTIVITIES

Trainings & Workshops

Mar. 2024- April 2024

Design Systems Bootcamp

A workshop camp leading professionals in an 8-week learning program, focused on helping teams learn how to build and launch a minimum viable product design using DSM.

InVision Corp.

Davao City, Philippines

Feb. 2023- Jun. 2023

Software Analysis Training

A training sponsored by Start-up Inc. which focused mainly on the theory and practice of software analysis, which lies in many software development processes.

Start-up Inc.

Zamboanga City, Philippines

February 2020

Work Immersion Program, Grade 12

On-the-job training for senior high school students, assigning them under different areas to experience the nature of the workplace.

Bureau of Fisheries and Aquatic Resources

Zamboanga City, Philippines

INTERESTS

Video-editing

Film making

Photography

Photo manipulation

AFFILIATIONS

Information Technology Honors Society, 2021-2024 Member

Western Mindanao State University, Student League of Designers, 2023 Contributor

Baliwasan Senior High School, Technologies Club, 2019-2020 Officer

International Philippine School in Riyadh, Campus Voice Publication, 2017 Officer

SKILLS

System Designing	Computer Expertise
C++, C, Eclipse, Java	TCP/IP networking
SQL Operating Systems	Microsoft Office packages
Windows Operating Systems	Microsoft Exchange Server
Linux Development	A variety of backup software

Languages

English	Conve	ersational	

Filipino Advanced conversational

REFERENCES

Mr. Cesar S. Morla Novasystems Incorporation Head Manager morlacesar@gmail.com (062) 143-6848 Ms. Pauleen Gregana Western Mindanao State University Course Adviser pauleen.gregana@gmail.com 0953 124 6128